&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：那么让我们跳到我们关于函数表达式的练习中。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So let's jump into our exercise on function expressions.
调出函数表达式练习的自述文件和ex.js。
Pull up the readme and the ex.js for the function expressions exercise.
在本练习中，
In this exercise,
你将会写一些函数，也会写一些函数表达式。
you're gonna be writing some functions and also some function expressions.
这些功能将管理一些学生注册记录
And these functions are gonna be managing some student enrollment records for
我们的车间。
our workshop.
这个练习的精神是，你将使用我们所学到的
The spirit of the exercise is that you're gonna be using what we've learned about
命名函数并尽可能使用函数。
named functions and using functions wherever possible.
所以你想要使用像地图和过滤器之类的东西
So you wanna be using things like map and filter and
寻找而不是你的老学校的循环。
find instead of your old school for loops.
你想在任何可能的地方使用函数。
You wanna use functions wherever possible.
这个练习分为两部分。
This is broken up into two parts, this exercise.
首先，完成第一部分，然后完成第二部分。
First, complete part one and then complete part two.
我们会回来的，当我们回来的时候，我们会解释这两个问题的解决方案
We'll come back, when we come back we will explain the solution for both so
你将有时间在这两个部分上工作。
you will have time to work on both parts.
在第一部分中，您要做的是编写一个函数声明和命名函数
In part one, what you're gonna do is write a function declarations and named function
根据这里的说明表达，我一会儿再看一遍。
expressions according to the instructions here, and I'll go over those in a moment.
在第二部分中，你要做的是重写
In part two, what you're going to do is rewrite
你做的所有这些功能都是箭头功能。
all of those functions that you did as arrow functions.
第一部分和第二部分的目的是
The purpose of part one and part two is for
您需要对代码可读性和可读性之间的差异进行并排比较
you to have a side by side comparison of the differences in code readability and
使用命名函数和使用箭头函数之间的功能，好吗？
functionality between using named functions and using arrow functions, okay?
所以在行为上不会有任何差异，
So there won't be any difference in behavior,
只是这两个部分之间代码风格的一个简单区别。
just simply a difference in code style between those two parts.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：您需要实现的主要功能是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The main functionality that you need to implement is that
有三个函数，称为printRecords，
there are three functions, called printRecords,
paidStudentsTo Enroll，很抱歉，请继续提醒Unpay。
paidStudentsToEnroll, and remain, I'm sorry, remindUnpaid.
这三个函数已经在ex.js文件中删除了。
Those three functions have been stubbed out in the ex.js file.
他们在那里等着你，你看到他们收到的是什么论点，我的意思是，
They're there for you, you see what they receive as arguments, I mean,
作为参数。
as parameters.
但您需要根据自述文件的内容实现这些内容。
But you need to implement those according to what the readme says.
您会注意到已经为您调用了这些函数，所以
And you'll notice that those functions are already called for you, so
这里我调用了printRecords。
here I've called printRecords.
我调用paidStudentsToEnroll，调用remindUnpay和
I call paidStudentsToEnroll and I call remindUnpaid and
预期的输出在此代码注释中。
the output that is expected is here in this code comment.
所以你的输出需要匹配这个输出，好吗？
So your output needs to match this output, okay?
printRecords的作用是获取学生ID的列表。
What printRecords does is it takes a list of student IDs.
所以就像你在这里看到的一样，需要一系列的学生证，
So it's gonna take an array of student IDs as you see here,
我们传入一个名为currentEnrollment的学生ID数组。
we are passing in an array of student IDs called currentEnrollment.
因此printRecords获取学生ID列表，并
So printRecords takes a list of student IDs and
需要检索每个学生记录。
needs to retrieve each student record.
这些存储在StudentRecords数组中。
Those are stored in the studentRecords array.
通过ID检索每条记录，那里有一个可以使用array find的提示。
Retrieve each record by ID, and there's a hint there than you can use array find.
按学生姓名排序，升序。
Sorted by the student name, ascending.
可以使用数组排序，但必须使用自定义函数。
You can use array sort, but you're gonna have to use a custom function.
然后将每条记录打印到控制台或控制台日志语句，包括
And then print each record to the console or the console log statement including
他们的名字，他们的身份证，以及他们是否得到了报酬。
their name, their ID, and whether or not they're paid.
这就是那个函数的作用。
That's what that function does.
第二，付费学生注册功能查看所有学生
Number two, the paid students to enroll function looks through all the student
记录和检查以查看其中是否有已支付但尚未注册的用户。
records and checks to see if any of them are paid but not yet enrolled.
这意味着它们还不在currentEnrollment数组中，
Meaning they're not yet in the currentEnrollment array,
他们的身份证不在那里。
their ID isn't there.
收集这些ID并
Collect those IDs and
然后返回一个包含先前注册的ID和新ID的新数组。
then return a new array with the previously enrolled IDs plus the new ones.
因此，它不会修改，它返回一个新的数组。
So, it doesn't modify, it returns a new array.
最后，提醒未支付的是，您将获得一份学生ID列表，
And finally, the remindUnpaid is you're gonna take a list of student IDs and
将该列表筛选为仅记录处于未付状态的列表。
filter that list to only ones whose records are in the unpaid status.
然后将该列表从第一项传递回我们的printRecords
And then pass that list back to our printRecords from item one
只打印出没有报酬的学生。
to print out only the students that are unpaid.
好的，这是练习的第一部分，再一次，第二部分，
Okay, so this is part one of the exercise and again, part two,
你不需要改变任何行为，你只需用箭头函数重写它。
you don't change any behavior, you just simply rewrite it with arrow functions.
一般来说，第一部分应该花你大约15分钟
Generally speaking, part one should take you about 15 minutes and
第二部分大约需要五分钟。
part two should take you about five minutes.
所以总的来说，我们大约需要20分钟来做这个练习。
So overall we would take about 20 minutes to do this exercise.
所以我们现在休息一下，让你们有机会练习第一部分和第二部分。
So we'll break now, let you have a chance to work on exercise part one and part two.
我建议将您的解决方案放在两个单独的文件中，以便
I'd recommend putting your solutions in two separate files so
你可以比较和对比它们。
that you can compare and contrast them.
我们稍后回来讨论这个练习的解决方案。
We'll come back in a little bit and talk through the solution to this exercise.
提醒你，如果你被困住了，你需要一点帮助
Reminder that if you get stuck and you need a little bit of a hand through you
就像作弊一样，解决方案文件位于EXfix-1和EXfix-2中。
just like to cheat, the solutions files are there in EXfix-1 and EXfix-2.